### **Personal Information**

- Pie de Boer
- **4** 17 December 1996
- ♠ Maastricht, The Netherlands
- Q Dutch

# Pie de Boer

# **Graduate - Data Science and Artificial Intelligence (BSc)**

# Contact

- A Berlin, Germany
- **1** +31618928452
- piedeboer96@gmail.com
- https://piedeboer96.github.io

Enthusiastic and creative graduate from Maastricht University with a strong interest in machine learning, signal processing, and generative Al. I possess excellent interpersonal skills and a solid technical mindset, thriving in both collaborative settings and individual research projects. In my spare time, I explore computer topics such as virtual machines, emulators, and Linux, delve into audio engineering, and engage in strength training.

### References

#### Dr. Prof. Pietro Bonizzi

Associate Professor Maastricht University pietro.bonizzi@maastrichtuniversity.nl

P. Bonizzi was my thesis supervisor

### **Education**

# ■ Data Science and Artificial Intelligence

Maastricht University, Maastricht | 2021 - 2024 Completed (180 ECTS)

Thesis: Conditional Diffusion Models for ECG Signal Denoising (8.5/10.0)

- ~ Trained using Google Cloud and PyTorch
- ~ Outperforming traditional signal processing methods found in MATLAB.

GPA: 8.28/10.0

## Competences

### **Programming Languages**

Java, Python, MATLAB, C++, Clojure, R, SQL, Bash

#### Stack

Google Cloud, Git, Unix, PyTorch, TensorFlow, Jupyter Notebook, Scikit-Learn, Homebrew and more.

#### **Soft Skills**

Presenting, Team Work, Gannt Chart

# **■** Chemistry

Utrecht University, Utrecht | 2016 - 2017

Completed first year (60 ECTS) GPA: 7.48/10.0

#### VWO - Atheneum

Bonnefantencollege HAVO/VWO, Maastricht | 2009 - 2016

Profile: Nature & Technology and Nature & Health

# Experience

## ■ Rabobank

## Research Project | 2023 - 2024

Completed a six-month research project on a quantum approach to portfolio optimization. Utilized Python and the D-Wave API to interface with actual quantum hardware. Maintained weekly communication with a senior data scientist and closely collaborated with a researcher from TNO.

### Self-Employed

#### Mathematics, Physics and Chemistry Tutor | 2019 - 2023

Tutored Dutch high school students in core science subjects from HAVO 3 to final exams, assisting up to seven students per week during peak times.

# **Additional Skills**

- ✓ English (C2) German (B2) Dutch (Native)
- **✓** MATLAB Fundamentals Certificate

# **Group Projects**



Golf Simulator 3D

Chess Engine

Multi Modal Assistant (Text, Speech and Vision)